<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Before Leaving AU</string>
    <string name="action_checklist">Checklist</string>
    <string name="image_desc">Task Images</string>
    <string name="task_title">Sample Task Title</string>
    <!--
      ~ The category names.
      -->
    <string name="category_what">What should I do?</string>
    <string name="category_why">Why should I do it?</string>
    <string name="category_how">How can I do it?</string>
    <!--
      ~ The task image names.
      -->
    <string-array name="task_image">
        <item>debt</item>
        <item>tax</item>
        <item>superannuation</item>
        <item>oshc</item>
        <item>transport</item>
        <item>deposit</item>
        <item>mobile</item>
        <item>car</item>
        <item>contracts</item>
        <item>backup</item>
        <item>verification</item>
        <item>reference</item>
        <item>sell</item>
        <item>shipping</item>
        <item>transfer</item>
        <item>close</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--
      ~ The task names.
      -->
    <string-array name="task_category">
        <item>Clear your debt</item>
        <item>Lodge the tax return</item>
        <item>Claim your superannuation</item>
        <item>Request a refund of your OSHC</item>
        <item>Return your transport card</item>
        <item>Claim your deposit</item>
        <item>Cancel your mobile plan</item>
        <item>Cancel your car insurance</item>
        <item>Cancel your contracts</item>
        <item>Make a backup of your files</item>
        <item>Get verification of AWLR</item>
        <item>Ask for letters of recommendation</item>
        <item>Sell you stuff</item>
        <item>Shipping things home</item>
        <item>Transfer money</item>
        <item>Close your bank account</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--
      ~ The details of the first category.
      -->
    <string-array name="category_what">
        <item>First things first, you will want to take care of any outstanding debt.</item>
        <item>First, you need to work out if you need to lodge a tax return. If needed, you should
            lodge a tax return to Australian Taxation Office before the due date.</item>
        <item>Superannuation, or super, is money put aside by your employer over your working life
            for you to live on when you retire from work.You should claim your superannuation if all
            required conditions are met.</item>
        <item>You can request a refund of your Overseas Student Health Cover (OSHC) if you meet the
            required conditions. For example, your OSHC has not expired if you are leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>If your are leaving Australia but you still have a positive balance on your myki, you can apply for a refund.</item>
        <item>If your lease is up, is there a deposit you can claim back? If your lease is not up yet,
            is there a penalty for abandoning your contract? You need to figure it out before leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>You should cancel your mobile plan before leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>If you have a car insurance, you should cancel it before leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>You should cancel all your contracts before leaving Australia including water,
            electricity, gas and Internet contract.</item>
        <item>You should make a backup of your files such as final year project before leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>In case you have worked in Australia and if you intend to apply for any benefit in
            your country, such as that of the migrant returned in Spain, do not forget to get the
            verification of working life residence in Australia.</item>
        <item>Yeah, it might be a bit awkward but chances are you took on some challenging work
            during your time in Australia. If you put in the effort, then you deserve a good reference.</item>
        <item>If you have been in Australia for years, you might have accumulated a lot of stuff.
            For those things you do not want to take home such as a TV or furniture, it is a good idea
            to start selling it off a month or so before you leave.</item>
        <item>If you have been in Australia for years, you might have accumulated a lot of stuff.
            You might have some things you would rather bring home with you. Find out if there is an
            import duty on these items. Particularly if it is something big like a car. You will need to
            calculate how much it will cost you to take the things you simply cannot part with.</item>
        <item>You should transfer your money out of your bank account if you decide to close it.</item>
        <item>if you have an Australia bank account, it might be a good idea to keep it open to make
            getting your tax refund and superannuation easier. However, once you have received them,
            you will want to close the account.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--
      ~ The details of the second category.
      -->
    <string-array name="category_why">
        <item>If you have any outstanding debt, you will not be allowed to close your Australian bank account.</item>
        <item>If you miss the due date, interest will apply to any amount you owe after the due date.</item>
        <item>Millions in unclaimed super is lost every year by people leaving the country unaware
            they can claim their contributions when they leave.</item>
        <item>A lot of money is lost every year by people leaving the country unaware
            they can request a refund of their OSHC when they leave.</item>
        <item>A lot of money is lost every year by people leaving the country unaware
            they can request a refund of their myki when they leave.</item>
        <item>This is what a good tenant should do and you can avoid a lot of unnecessary trouble
            for yourself and your landlord if you do it before leaving Australia.</item>
        <item>If you forget to cancel your mobile plan before leaving Australia, you will still be
            charged or receive bill from your mobile provider monthly.</item>
        <item>You will still be charged by your insurance company and you may lose the chance to
            apply for a refund if you do it too late.</item>
        <item>You will still be charged after leaving Australia if you forget to do it.</item>
        <item>Your access to University systems such as your student email account will be deactivated
            half year to one year after your graduation, so your important documents will be lost
            if you do not make a backup of them.</item>
        <item>This information is needed if you either have applied to have your Australian pension
            paid outside Australia or want to get a pension under a social security agreement with
            another country.</item>
        <item>This will help your chances when you go to find a job back home or in your next destination.</item>
        <item>You do not have to do this if you have nothing to sell.</item>
        <item>You do not have to do this if everything you want to take home can be carry-on.</item>
        <item>Most banks, when closing your account, would like to see the account being at zero before they proceed with the closure.</item>
        <item>Why? Well, If you do decide to continue using your Australia bank account think about
            the hassle; fees, change of address, online banking and the various costs for using your card outside of Australia.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--
      ~ The details of the third category.
      -->
    <string-array name="category_how">
        <item>Fines, loans and other bills should be taken care of before you leave.</item>
        <item>You can either use the Do I need to lodge a tax return tool in ATO online
            services through your myGov account or access the web-based tool to help you work out
            if you need to lodge a tax return. If needed, you can choose from of the following
            options depending on your circumstances. First, you can odge your tax return online
            with myTax – this is the quick, safe and secure way to prepare and lodge your own return.
            Second, you can lodge your tax return with a registered tax agent. Third, you can
            lodge a paper tax return.</item>
        <item>Information on the ATO website can help you work out if you meet all required conditions
            to claim your super. To claim your super directly from your super fund, fill out a
            Departing Australia Superannuation Payment (DASP) application form online.</item>
        <item>You can either submit a paper refund request form or a digital refund request form to
            your OSHC provider directly.</item>
        <item>You can either apply for a refund online or visit the public transport hub to apply for a refund.</item>
        <item>No matter your lease is up or not, you should make sure you request it to your landlord
            early enough to get it by the time you leave.</item>
        <item>You can cancel your mobile plan via a call or on the app of your mobile provider.</item>
        <item>Cancelling your car insurance is generally a simple process. Depending on who you are
            insured with, you might be able to cancel it online, which is the easiest way to do it.
            However, lots of insurance companies want to speak to the policy holder to cancel,
            if that is the case, you will need to call your insurance company.</item>
        <item>To cancel your contract, it is simple. First, you should contact your water/energy/Internet
            provider either over the phone or online. Next, you need to provide  the right information
            such as your account number and proof of identification. Finally, pay an exit fee and any outstanding bills.</item>
        <item>You should download your account data from University systems to your PC or upload to the cloud.</item>
        <item>You can get it through Centrelink completing the form verification of working life
            residence in Australia (AUS027).</item>
        <item>You will want to choose someone who can confidently write about your career and talents
            in a convincing way, so choose your references based on those who know you best. And it
            is generally best to send your request for a recommendation in a polite way as early as you can.</item>
        <item>There are many websites or apps where you can sell your stuff such as Gumtree, Facebook Marketplace and eBay.</item>
        <item>There are many international shipping companies which can help you ship things home such as DHL, FedEx and UPS.</item>
        <item>When it comes to transferring money, there are a few options. Ideally you will still
            have your bank account from your home country and you can transfer it to that or to a
            family member. If not, it is recommended that you use a money transfer service. Bank to
            bank transfers can sometimes cost you a small fortune, so check out fees before you try
            something like this.</item>
        <item>You can close your bank account either over a call or on the bank mobile app.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>